Let's eat something red.
赤いもの食べよう
Let's eat.
食べよう
There's something red.
赤いものあるもんね
What do you eat?
何食べる?
What shall we eat?
何食べよう
Salmon?
サーモン?
Salmon is not good.
サーモンうまくないよ
picture?
え?
Salmon is not good.
サーモンうまくないよ
It's sweet soy sauce.
甘い醤油だ
Try lowering it.
下出してみて
Here?
ここで?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
yeah?
ん?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
After all, you have to do it directly.
やっぱ直接しないとダメだわ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Lick the first step.
先一歩舐めて
Look here.
こっち見て
Look at me and lick me hard.
こっち見てしっかり舐めて
It feels so good.
すっごい気持ちいい
Make it more intense.
もっと激しくして
Use your hands too.
手も使って
Is it okay to do that?
そんなことしていい?
Open your mouth.
口開けて
show me.
見せて
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
I've got my clothes on.
服ついちゃったじゃん
What?
え、何?
Can I laugh with you?
一緒に笑ってもいいですか?
That's amazing.
すごいね
what happened?
どうしたの?
picture?
え?
I said who are you?
誰ですかって言ってたから
Oh, this person?
あ、この人?
Oh, something behind me.
え、なんか後ろに
This person has a camera.
この人は、ちょっとカメラこそ
Because it's cute.
可愛いから
I want to take pictures of cute girls.
可愛い子撮りたい
It's cute.
可愛いね
Because it's cute.
可愛 い から
You did something weird a while ago.
なんかさっき、変なことしてたでしょ
At the door.
玄関で
They found out, because I was filming it.
バ レたってか、俺撮ってたから
What, all of a sudden?
何、あれ、急に
What, what, naughty?
何、何、エッチなの?
Did you want to do something naughty?
エッチなことしたかったの?
No, hmm.
いや、うーん
It's a bit embarrassing, so...
恥ずかしいから、ちょっと
What do you usually do now?
今、普段何してるんだっけ?
Usually at university.
普段、大学で
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Eh, what grade are you in?
え、何年生?
Now, 1.
今、1
Ah, I see.
あ、そっか
I only arrived in the spring.
春から入っただけ
oh yeah.
そうそう
It's a women's university.
女子大だよね
What about women's colleges?
女子大どうですか?
Is it fun?
楽しいですか?
There are only girls, right?
女子しかいないでしょ?
Yes, only girls.
うん、女子だけ
Isn't it boring?
なんか、つまんなくない?
That's not true.
そんなことない
Really?
本当に?
After all, you like men, right?
だって、男好きでしょ?
picture?
え?
Is your boyfriend here?
彼氏、いんの?
not present.
いない
So, you came to Tokyo?
あれ、上京してきたんだっけ?
Hokkaido.
北海道
That's why it's so white.
だから、すごい白いんだね
It's so curvy.
プリプリだしね
It kind of looks like seafood.
なんか、海鮮みたいだよね
海鮮
What is your favorite seafood?
好きな海鮮は?
Salmon.
サーモン
Salmon?
サーモン?
Yeah.
うん
Sorry, there's salmon.
ごめんね、サーモンあるとか
I didn't mean to deceive you.
騙したつもりないんだけど
Right now, he's buying salmon for me at the convenience store.
今、彼がコンビニでサーモン買ってきてくれてるから、
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってて
I see.
そっか
Do you have a part-time job?
バイトとかしてる?
Yes, I have a part-time job.
うん、バイトしてる
What are you doing?
何してる?
Cram school instructor.
塾講師
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Tell me what kind of person you are.
どういう人を教えて
Junior high school student.
中学生
Hey.
へー
What do you think?
どうですか?
hard?
大変?
Yeah, it's okay.
うん、大丈夫
I'm sorry, but the hourly wage is good, right?
ちょっとごめんね、時給はいいんでしょ?
You're smart.
頭いいんだね
Don't you get confessed to by middle school students?
中学生に告白されたりしない?
Well, that's true.
いやー、それはさすがに
You'll do it, right?
するでしょ、こんだけ
cute.
かわいい
So cute, this is it.
かわいい、こんだけ
If only it were this curvy.
こんだけプリプリだったら
A person who does things properly.
ちゃんとしてる人
Someone who does it properly?
ちゃんとしてる人?
I'm doing it right.
俺、ちゃんとしてるよ
TRUE?
本当?
I was just looking at it,
さっき見てたらさ、
Ah, because he's not here.
あ いついないからさ
Are you not there?
いないの?
He's trying to buy some saury.
あいつ、サンマ買ってみてるから
Let's have sex with this.
俺、これとエッチしようよ
I'll be back.
帰ってきちゃうよ
I'll finish it before you get back.
帰ってくる前に終わらすから
I felt like I was about to eat something just now.
さっきなんか、 食べそうだったから
It's going to be a little painful.
ちょっと 苦しいしちゃうから
picture?
え?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It looks like she's going to be a voice actor.
声 優さんになりそうだよね
I guess so.
そうかな
mosquito
か
Okay.
わ いい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
picture?
え?
cute?
かわいい?
Hey, it's cute.
ね え、かわいいね
amazing.
すごい
like.
好き
good
好
tree.
き
It's embarrassing.
恥 ずかしい
cold.
冷たい
Huh?
あれ?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Wow, hey.
すごい、ちょっと
Show me a little.
ちょっと 見せて
That's amazing though.
すごいんだけど
I'll put it on properly.
ちゃんとつけちゃう
This is also getting sticky.
これもペトペトになってるよ
What is this?
なにこれ?
Are you excited?
興奮してる?
Were you excited?
興奮してたでしょ?
He's coming back, so wait a minute.
あいつ帰ってきちゃうから、ちょっと
I bought some eggs.
卵買ってきましたよ
What are you doing?
何やってんの?
You're early, man.
早いよ、お前
It's early.
早いよ
Because I'm having sex.
エッチしてるから
I'm back.
帰ってきちゃったよ
Shall I show it to you?
見せつけてやろうか
Why is that so cool?
なんでかっこいいじゃん
how?
どうやって?
どう やって?
why?
なんで?
shame
恥
That's embarrassing.
ず かしい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
mosquito
か
It's cool.
っ こいい
かっこいいよ
I'm so hungry.
お腹すげえ
Maybe both.
どっちもかも
amazing.
すごい
That's a really nice essence.
めっちゃいいエッスね
Resolutely.
しみじみ
I'm sleeping a lot.
すごい寝てるよ
Very salty.
すごいしょっぱい
It's so salty.
すごいしょっぱいよ
A lot of sweat.
すごい汗
Are you nervous?
緊張してんの?
It's a beautiful body.
きれいな体だね
Amazing, beautiful.
すごい、美しい
beautiful.
美しい
What are you hiding?
何隠してるの?
I'll show it to that guy over there.
あそこのお兄さんに見せてあげる
Those are cute boobs.
かわいいおっぱいだね
Don't do that.
そう いうことやらないで
Can I check?
確かめていいですか?
Want to check?
確かめたい?
Shall I check?
確かめちゃう?
I have no hair.
お毛毛がない
No, no, no.
だめだめだめ
だ めだめだめ
It's staining.
しみになってるよ
Shiny.
テカテカ
I'll take this home.
これ持って帰ります
I'll take it home.
持って帰りまーす
It's Kaho.
カホですよ
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's a beautiful body.
きれいな体だね
I hid it again.
また隠した
So sexy.
すごいセクシー
Look at the camera.
カメラ見てほら
カメラ見て
Dress in such an embarrassing manner.
こんな恥ずかしい格好して
That's not true.
そんなことないでしょ
This wasn't happening in Hokkaido, was it?
こんなこと北海道じゃなかったでしょ
It was there.
あったね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Yeah.
うん
Ume.
うめー
You've never seen the insides of your feet so clearly.
こんな足の中が、 パックリ見えることないよね
I'm sleeping a lot.
すごい寝てるよ
Now put your finger in it.
今指入れてみろよ
Stand up in here.
立 ってさ、この中
Huh?
あれ?
There's a great atmosphere.
すごい空気が入ってるね
It's small.
狭いね
But I'm being pushed out.
押し出されるんだけど
That's amazing.
すごいよ
It was very small.
狭かったっすよ
Should I open it myself?
自分で開いと?
Oh, so in the middle.
あ、すごい真ん中
It's in the middle.
真ん中じゃん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
It's no good.
駄目だよ
Are you laughing?
笑ってんの?
I'm really falling asleep.
すごい寝ちゃってるよ
Try putting your finger in it.
指入れてみろよ
It's amazing, all the way.
すごいよ、奥まで
That's terrible.
やばいっすね
Can you see a little deeper?
ちょっと奥まで見える?
It's amazing, all the way.
すごいよ、奥まで
I can see deep inside.
奥まで見えるよ
I want to become a doctor.
お医者さんになってみたい
He's a doctor.
お医者さんだよ
Do you know this?
こういうの知ってる?
I went in.
入っちゃった
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
It was inside, all the way.
入ってったよ、奥まで
Strong pushing force.
押し出す力が強い
Awesome, amazing.
すごいすごい
I wonder if it will be born?
生まれるんじゃないかな?
It seems like it will come out again.
また出てきそう
Looks like it's going to be born.
生まれそう
amazing.
すごい
Amazing, it went all the way in.
すごい、奥まで入っちゃった
It's moving amazingly.
すごい 動いてる
Oisho.
おいしょ
delicious.
おいしい
Brother, brother.
お兄さん、お兄さん
It's moving a lot.
すごい動いてる
Okay, okay.
よしよし
amazing.
すごい
Sister, sister, please try to sleep.
お姉さん、お姉さん、寝てみて
yes.
はい
That's amazing.
すごいね
Dad, Chi
お父さん、ち
Hmm, when I look at you, you look happy.
ん ちん見たら嬉しそうな顔してるね
Here, let me touch you.
ほら、触ってもらおうか
Awesome, I'll lick it.
すごい、舐めてくる
Touch it.
手触って
Which one is delicious?
どっちがおいしい?
I want you to do it.
やってほしい
I want you to do it, I licked it.
やって ほ しい、舐めたよ
Please go first.
先 に行ってください
good?
いい?
I wish you the best.
頑張ってください
Is it okay to leave it like this?
このままでいい?
There isn't.
ないよ
By mouth.
口で
amazing.
すごい
That's amazing.
すごいね
I'm going to sleep, I'm going to sleep
寝るから寝たから
hey.
ね
Can you move?
動 けるの?
I want you to sleep.
寝てほしい
amazing.
すごい
It's early.
早いよ
I want you to sleep.
寝てほしい
Move it.
動かして
What is it?
何だよ
I was worried about something.
何だか悩んだよ
I won't push it anymore.
もう、押しないからね
If you don't push it, it will become shabby.
押しなきゃシャーヴィー的になる
Amazing, top and bottom.
すごいね、上も下も
That's amazing.
すごいね
what are you doing?
何してるの?
I was watching the shower.
シャワー見てたの
Did you watch the shower?
シャワー見てたの?
I'll let you bathe.
浴びさせてあげるね
how was it?
どうだった?
How was it?
どうだったの?
Good.
よかったよ
To two men.
二人の男にね
Good for you.
よ かったね
よかったね
Did you like which dick is better?
どっちのチンチンがいいのか、好きでした?
Both.
どっちも
Teka
テカ
Teka.
テ カ
Shiny.
テカテカ
This, this, this.
これ、これ、これ
Haven't you done that much?
そんなにやったことないの?
Huh?
あれ?
what happened?
どうしたの?
My muscles are so weak.
こんな、 筋肉が弱まれて
nice.
いいね
いい ね
That's amazing.
すごいね
It went down.
下がった
a little bit.
ちょっと
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
blood
チ
It's hard.
ンチ ンがね
Again, don't settle for a second.
またちょっと、決着つけないでね
Even though I released it, I still don't know.
出したのに、まだ分からない
Chin Chin is surrounded everywhere.
どこにも、チンチンが囲まれてる
Looks like fun.
楽しそうだね
Well, it's both.
こうじゃ、両方さ
I can do both.
両方いけるな
It's luxurious.
贅沢にね
luxury.
贅沢
Cock?
チンポ?
Cock.
チンポ
Double cock?
ダブルチンポ?
Double cock.
ダブルチンポ
Which one is delicious?
どっちがおいしいの?
Both.
どっちも
nice.
いいね
It looks delicious but it's no good.
おいしそうにダメやんけ
No way.
ダメやんけ
I can't eat sesame anymore.
ごまできなくなっちゃった
I want you to find out.
つけ出してほしい
delicious?
おいしい?
delicious.
おいしい
oh.
おー
Oh, that's amazing.
おー、すごい
Do you want to say it again?
また言いたいかな?
Do you want to say it?
言 いたいかな?
That's fine.
いいですよ
Nice, nice.
いいな、いいな
It must feel good.
気持ちいいだろうね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
mosquito
カ
Let's have a look at the mail.
メ ラ見てもらおう
Amazing, again.
すごいね、また
delicious?
おいしい?
delicious.
おいしい
delicious?
おいしい?
Really delicious.
本当においしい
Which one is delicious?
どっちがおいしいの?
Both.
どっちも
It's very delicious.
すごくおいしい
No.
ダ メ
That's no good.
ダメだね
Why is it so bad?
なんでこんなにダメなの?
Wait a minute, I'm not going to go here.
ちょっと待って、ここでいけなくなっちゃおう
home.
いえ
Marumie?
まるみえ?
picture?
え?
Is it Marumien?
まるみえなの?
I won't say it because it's difficult.
難しいから言わない
Is it difficult?
難しいの?
I can't even do it.
まるかもできないよ
Shall we go already?
もういっちゃおう?
Let's go already.
もういっちゃおう
here
ここ
I haven't gone that far.
まで いってないですよ
That's enough.
もういいだろ
This is what I saw until the end.
最後まで見てたらこうしてました
That's enough.
もういいだろ
Isn't it good for seniors?
先輩の方もいいじゃないですか
Violently.
激しく
I think I'll go again.
またいきそう
Open your mouth.
口を開けて
I cum in her mouth again.
また口の中出しちゃった
What did it taste like?
どんな味でした?
sweet.
甘い
Good, you.
いいな、お前
Why did you drink?
なんで飲んだの?
It's cute.
かわいいですもん
Good, you.
いいな、お前
Psychos.
サイコス
good morning.
おはよう
You're fine.
お前もういいよ
お 前もういいよ